Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is vanilla pecan blondie. Let me
show you how to make it. In your Ninja
Creamy Pint, you are going to combine
400 g of a fat-free high protein milk,
40 to 45 g of a sugar substitute, 1/4
teaspoon of salt, 1/4 teaspoon of
zantham gum, and then about a teaspoon
of vanilla bean paste. Blend that all
together, throw it in the freezer for at
least 16 hours. Take it out, run under
hot water for about a minute, and then
throw it in your creamy on the light ice
cream setting. Now, here is where the
mixins come into play. I'm using one of
these Alpha Prime Bites protein
brownies. Look how moist this thing is.
That is ridiculous for a protein snack.
These things are awesome. If your creamy
comes out powdery like mine did, you can
just take it out and scrape on the sides
with a butter knife and then run it on
the respin setting. I actually ran mine
on the mix-in setting because I could
tell it was almost done. And if you
didn't know, the mix-in setting runs for
less time and at a slower rate than the
respin setting. And then all you have to
do is top it with your brownies, pecans,
and caramel.